‎BEWARE FIRE
‎CIGARETTE BUTTS HERE
‎KEEP CLOSED
‎Yo, Sasaki.
‎Hello.
‎The hell, man?
‎I couldn't find you in the smoking room
‎downstairs, so I had to come looking.
‎Sorry.
‎Is everything all right?
‎The department manager
‎wants a meeting after this.
‎For God's sake.
‎Another pointless meeting that could
‎have been an email that will go on and on…
‎All right, all right.
‎I just wanna go home.
‎Me too.
‎HAPPY CORP.
‎PUT SNACKS HERE
‎LOCAL
‎OPEN 24 HOURS - SUPER S
‎SUPER S
‎HALF PRICE - SQUID AND CHINESE RADISH
‎ALCOHOL SECTION
‎CRACKERS
‎TASTY RICE CRACKERS
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎Hello, and welcome!
‎Do you have a point card?
‎Yes, I do.
‎Thank you.
‎Here is your card back.
‎Would you like a bag?
‎Just the three-yen one, please.
‎With the bag, your total comes to 883 yen.
‎Here.
‎Here is your change.
‎Thank you.
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎CASHIER: YAMADA
‎Yamada from register two.
‎My ray of light
‎at the end of a long work day.
‎Then again…
‎I'm dropping by way too much these days,
‎even when I don't really need anything.
‎What a stupid purchase I've made.
‎I might as well bring a gift
‎for Yamada while I'm at it.
‎She might actually like that.
‎TASTY RICE CRACKERS
‎Wow! Thank you so much!
‎Guess it's delusional old men like me
‎who go around causing awkward situations.
‎What the hell
‎is going on with you, Sasaki?
‎Did you suddenly forget that doing client
‎rounds doesn't equate to a nice stroll?
‎For God's sake, man.
‎You gotta let me know about these things!
‎I'm very sorry, sir.
‎Use your words, Sasaki!
‎Remember to use your words!
‎People are gonna ask
‎if I'm fit to manage--
‎Sir. Sorry to interrupt.
‎Eda from Square Corp.
‎is asking about that quote.
‎Tell him we'll respond sometime tomorrow.
‎So terribly sorry to keep you waiting!
‎Yes. It'll be ready tomorrow.
‎Yes. Yes. I am truly sorry…
‎Meeting at seven!
‎That idiot running the department…
‎Not only did we run until midnight,
‎but also, nothing even got resolved.
‎I'm gonna kill--
‎Nobody.
‎It's times like these…
‎Especially times like these…
‎I need Yamada tonight!
‎Here is your change, deary.
‎GLOOM
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎Thank you.
‎Yamada must be on her break,
‎or gone home for the day.
‎Things are just not going my way today.
‎Please, nicotine. Don't fail me today.
‎Ew, look.
‎-Disgusting.
‎-Let's go.
‎Don't tell me there's no smoking area?
‎You have got to be kidding me.
‎Since when did us smokers
‎lose all our basic rights?
‎Hey, pops.
‎Over here.
‎Come join me for a drag.
‎Such an attractive--
‎Wait,
‎is this the backside of the supermarket?
‎Won't you get in trouble
‎for letting an outsider smoke here?
‎Who's gonna tell
‎if you're an outsider or not?
‎Well, then… I guess I'll join you.
‎Please do.
‎Not sure what scene she's into,
‎but she sure does look intense.
‎Certainly doesn't
‎look like she works here.
‎So, ma'am. Which section
‎of the supermarket do you work--
‎Come on. Gimme a light.
‎Why else do you think I called you over?
‎Then you should have just said so!
‎I felt like joshing with you.
‎You shouldn't "josh"
‎someone you've only just met.
‎You're the guy who's always
‎lining up at register two, ain't ya?
‎Am I? Must be coincidence.
‎Is it also a coincidence that you line up
‎even when other registers are open?
‎She knows my whole routine.
‎You like Little Miss Yamada, don't you?
‎She already knows the answer,
‎and still she chooses to tease me?
‎I get it.
‎She's a sweet girl, that Yamada.
‎Nice on the eyes, and a nice rack to boot.
‎And she's single,
‎which must delight you, no?
‎That's not true!
‎Yes, I know I'm just some creepy guy
‎who likes to line up at Yamada's register.
‎But honestly, it's just that her
‎work ethic is what keeps me going!
‎That's all I'm allowed
‎to be "delighted" about!
‎Sorry.
‎I got a bit carried away there.
‎-Well, that's a relief.
‎-Huh?
‎I thought Yamada
‎had herself another shitty customer.
‎She gets a lot of idiots
‎pestering her about that sort of thing.
‎But you're not like that.
‎Work hard, and stay sophisticated, Sasaki.
‎I thought she was just an ill-mannered
‎young lady who picks on older men,
‎but it would seem she's a good kid
‎who looks out for her coworkers.
‎Um…
‎Excuse me, but you need to pay.
‎Sorry.
‎Mr. Sasaki?
‎Huh? How do you know my name?
‎I've known your name for a while now
‎because of your point card.
‎I wanted to thank you.
‎I've been speaking with Tayama.
‎-I'm very happy to hear it.
‎-Huh?
‎She says you're a fan of mine.
‎You dropped your card.
‎Sorry about that.
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎Goddamn it, Tayama.
‎Don't think I won't remember that name!
‎Yo. I'm Tayama.
‎See you at the smoking area, Sasaki.
‎Actually, how did Tayama know my name?
‎HAPPY CORP.
‎Another meeting
‎till midnight tonight, huh?
‎I hope someone goes apeshit
‎and trashes the meeting for us.
‎Meeting this, meeting that.
‎About what, even?
‎SMOKING ROOM
‎Everyone's on edge
‎from all these back-to-back meetings.
‎Even me…
‎But I've got the best pick-me-up!
‎The smile of Yamada
‎from Super S register two!
‎Hello, and welcome!
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎You're the guy who's always
‎lining up at register two, ain't ya?
‎She's not here.
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎Oh, what brilliant timing!
‎She says you're a fan of mine.
‎Next, please.
‎Hello, and welcome!
‎Just these, please.
‎All right. Do you have a point card?
‎-I do.
‎-Thank you.
‎Here's your card back.
‎I've been speaking with Tayama.
‎She says you're a fan of mine.
‎Sir? Sir?
‎Yes?
‎That'll be 883 yen.
‎Sorry.
‎I exposed myself
‎as a gross and bumbling idiot,
‎but I'm glad she still chose
‎to serve me politely.
‎I'm the only one getting weird about this!
‎Moron! Idiot!
‎From now on, I'm going to just
‎quietly get on with my shopping.
‎Do as you see fit.
‎That client still hasn't gotten
‎back to me after I sent that apology.
‎I'm gonna die
‎without ever seeing my family again.
‎KEEP THINGS TIDY AND IN ORDER
‎Next to this old geezer.
‎Would you give it a rest already?
‎And why are you here
‎doing overtime anyway?
‎I'm fixing up those files the newbie did.
‎Are you letting them walk all over you?
‎No, they really shouldn't have given this
‎sort of work to a newbie to begin with.
‎That department manager, am I right?
‎"Throw 'em in the deep end.
‎That's the best way to learn."
‎Then he leaves the mess
‎they make to everyone else.
‎Well, either way,
‎the poor newbie's got it the hardest.
‎I can tell by these files
‎that a lot of heart went into this.
‎And besides… I've got my pick-me-up.
‎Hello, and welcome!
‎This is nothing when I know I've got--
‎Oh? It's Mr. Fan.
‎I just deleted all my updates!
‎This calls for a celebration!
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎Thanks. You too.
‎She wasn't there.
‎It's like the universe is saying,
‎"Serves you right, Sasaki,
‎for seeking solace through others."
‎I really need to find
‎a hobby or something.
‎Sasaki.
‎'Sup?
‎The smoking spot's empty, you know?
‎Wanna join me?
‎Tayama! I… have a bone to pick with you.
‎How could you?
‎You told Yamada I was a fan of hers.
‎Now I'm too embarrassed
‎to line up at her register.
‎But you still line up for her.
‎How did you see that?
‎Sorry for being a meanie, Sasaki.
‎But Yamada was very happy to hear it.
‎She said it herself, right?
‎I'm not some kid who takes
‎everything at face value. You know?
‎Is that the only bone you had to pick?
‎And…
‎Here. These are for you.
‎TASTY RICE CRACKERS
‎As thanks for letting me
‎smoke with you the other day.
‎Hey, nice!
‎You know them? "Tasty Rice Crackers."
‎I love them.
‎These are really popular
‎with the old folks, huh?
‎Am I really that old to her?
‎I've been meaning to try these.
‎Thanks, Sasaki.
‎Well, don't just stand there.
‎Come smoke next to me.
‎Oh? She likes her gift
‎from an elderly fellow?
‎Tayama. Do you like things
‎that have come full circle?
‎I'm a little hungry after my shift.
‎Well, don't eat them all.
‎Wouldn't want to strain
‎yourself before bed--
‎I left my smokes back at work.
‎I'm flat out.
‎Here. You can have mine.
‎No, I couldn't ask that of you.
‎Take it.
‎Tayama?
‎If it's in the way of your crackers,
‎just say so.
‎Wow, Sasaki. Very perceptive.
‎Do you enjoy teasing old men, Tayama?
‎Very much so.
‎I'll bet it's fun!
‎Can you blame me?
‎You're like my stress relief.
‎What? Stress relief?
‎Just like how you
‎line up for Yamada's register.
‎Now you're teasing me again.
‎Unlike you, I don't pick on Yamada.
‎You don't get it, do you?
‎We all have our different
‎ways of relieving stress.
‎So please don't pout.
‎I hope I'll see you again, Sasaki.
‎I'm not pouting.
‎Morning.
‎PUT SNACKS HERE
‎TASTY RICE CRACKERS
‎How was the client?
‎Oh, yeah. I'm a master apologizer,
‎so we got it all worked out.
‎Are these rice crackers yours?
‎How did you know?
‎Are you brain-dead?
‎Do you even know how many times
‎you've made me eat these?
‎Once you start,
‎you can't just stop at one with these.
‎They go well with alcohol.
‎You should take them home with you.
‎I will! I'll be taking the whole bag!
‎But why do you have so many?
‎Did you buy in bulk, or something?
‎I kind of just got them
‎when I went to the supermarket.
‎I forgot I already bought some,
‎so now I have extra.
‎What? Then just stop buying them.
‎But then I won't have a reason
‎to go to the supermarket.
‎Then stop going to the supermarket!
‎OPEN 24 HOURS - SUPER S
‎CRACKERS
‎Just stop buying them, okay?
‎Hello, and welcome!
‎You're always getting these.
‎They're delicious, right?
‎Huh?
‎You like them too?
‎I do.
‎But only just recently.
‎Somebody gave me some to try,
‎and I found they were so delicious.
‎I couldn't stop at just one.
‎Somebody gave her some?
‎They're good rice crackers.
‎Could it be… Could it be?
‎Could Yamada and Tayama be…
‎They must be really good friends.
‎Try these.
‎Wow. Thank you!
‎Yamada. Do you have allergies?
‎No.
‎It's probably just some dense old guy
‎getting delusional about me.
‎Subtitle translation by: Rychelle Brittain